<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hTWOo on Veni, Vidi, Vici</title>
    <link>https://juliemturner.net/tags/htwoo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hTWOo on Veni, Vidi, Vici</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>julie.turner@sympraxisconsulting.com (Julie Turner)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>julie.turner@sympraxisconsulting.com (Julie Turner)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Julie Turner ~ All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:08:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juliemturner.net/tags/htwoo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>hTWOo-React 2.1.0 Spotlight: Dialogs</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/htwoo-210-dialogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>julie.turner@sympraxisconsulting.com (Julie Turner)</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/htwoo-210-dialogs/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve just released the latest version of hTWOo-React, version 2.1. I&amp;rsquo;m going to be posting various updates highlighting some of the new updates over the next several weeks, so please check back or follow me on LinkedIn for more updates. For more information on hTWOo-React check out our documentation. For an overview of hTWOo please see this previous post or visit our hTWOo page.
Dialogs in SPFx just got EASY My absolute favorite update to hTWOo-Core 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to hTWOo-React: Microsoft Fluent UI React alternative</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/intro-htwoo-react/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>julie.turner@sympraxisconsulting.com (Julie Turner)</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/intro-htwoo-react/</guid>
      <description>Getting Stared with hTWOo-React presentation This PnP Community demo is taken from the Viva Connections &amp;amp; SharePoint Framework Bi-weekly sync call recorded on January 12, 2023.
I recently had the opportunity to present a &amp;ldquo;Getting Started with hTWOo React&amp;rdquo; session on the bi-weekly Viva Connections &amp;amp; SharePoint Framework call. I always love being able to present the fun stuff I&amp;rsquo;m working on to the rest of the community. For those of you who are not familiar, hTWOo is an open source alternative for Microsoft’s Fluent UI Web Design system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
