<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Extending SharePoint with ADAL and the Microsoft Graph API on Veni, Vidi, Vici</title>
    <link>https://juliemturner.net/series/extending-sharepoint-with-adal-and-the-microsoft-graph-api/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Extending SharePoint with ADAL and the Microsoft Graph API on Veni, Vidi, Vici</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>julie.turner@sympraxisconsulting.com (Julie Turner)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>julie.turner@sympraxisconsulting.com (Julie Turner)</webMaster>
    <copyright>Julie Turner ~ All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 21:26:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juliemturner.net/series/extending-sharepoint-with-adal-and-the-microsoft-graph-api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Streamline ADAL implementation: Extending SharePoint with the Microsoft Graph – Part 4</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/extending-sharepoint-with-adal-and-the-microsoft-graph-api-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 13:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>julie.turner@sympraxisconsulting.com (Julie Turner)</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/extending-sharepoint-with-adal-and-the-microsoft-graph-api-part-4/</guid>
      <description>Introduction When I last left you (in Part 3) we had completed the round-trip journey that is learning all the facets to accessing the Microsoft Graph API (MSGraph) through an Azure Application and the ADAL.js library. A significant portion of our time was spent simply on the different ways to leverage ADAL.js depending on the framework you were using. In this next installment we&amp;rsquo;re going to go one step further and streamline our implementation of ADAL, in AngularJS specifically, but with broader implications to any web based framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Results: Extending SharePoint with ADAL and the Microsoft Graph API - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/extending-sharepoint-with-adal-and-the-microsoft-graph-api-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 14:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>julie.turner@sympraxisconsulting.com (Julie Turner)</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/extending-sharepoint-with-adal-and-the-microsoft-graph-api-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In Part 1, I discussed the background and setup information you would need to successfully embark on a client site widget for SharePoint that accesses the Microsoft Graph API (MSGraphAPI). In Part 2, we went in depth to the various ways of utilizing the adal.js and adal-angular.js libraries for authentication. Now, here in Part 3 we’re going to get right into the nuts and bolts of a real solution that does the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADAL authorization: Extending SharePoint with the Microsoft Graph – Part 2</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/extending-sharepoint-with-adal-and-the-microsoft-graph-api-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 14:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>julie.turner@sympraxisconsulting.com (Julie Turner)</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/extending-sharepoint-with-adal-and-the-microsoft-graph-api-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In Part 1 of this series I covered all the setup needed to start your Microsoft Graph API (MSGraphAPI) client side widget. In Part 2, we’re going to dive into the many ways to use adal.js and its counterpart adal-angular.js. I’ve included the same resources I included in Part 1, under the section for ADAL you’ll find a lot of references to Cloud Identity blog by Vittorio Bertocci who has blogged extensively on the library, explaining in depth the technical workings of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started: Extending SharePoint with ADAL and the Microsoft Graph API – Part 1</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/extending-sharepoint-with-adal-and-the-microsoft-graph-api-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 13:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>julie.turner@sympraxisconsulting.com (Julie Turner)</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/extending-sharepoint-with-adal-and-the-microsoft-graph-api-part-1/</guid>
      <description>When Marc and I were at Ignite this past September, #SharePoint was the most tweeted hashtag. We heard a lot about the new SharePoint Framework (SPFx), which was clearly the focus for developers. But another oft-discussed technology topic centered on the expansion of the Microsoft Graph API (MSGraphAPI). It’s clearly going to be the API of choice going forward to access all Office 365 content, but its maturity is still early days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
