<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

	<!-- generator="WordPress/6.1.1" created="2022-12-08 21:04" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/"
>

<channel>
	<title>Veni, Vidi, Vici</title>
	<link>https://julieturner.net</link>
	<description>Musings and Solutions for SharePoint, Microsoft 365, and Azure</description>
	<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 21:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>https://julieturner.net</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>https://julieturner.net</wp:base_blog_url>

		<wp:author><wp:author_id>1</wp:author_id><wp:author_login><![CDATA[jturnerwp]]></wp:author_login><wp:author_email><![CDATA[julie@julieturner.net]]></wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[Julie Turner, MVP]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[Julie]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[Turner]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>

				
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://julieturner.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/cropped-julieturner_icon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Veni, Vidi, Vici</title>
	<link>https://julieturner.net</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">116959429</site>
		<item>
		<title><![CDATA[Privacy Policy]]></title>
		<link>https://julieturner.net/privacy-policy/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 16:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jturnerwp]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://julieturner.net/?page_id=692</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Who we are</h2><p>Our website address is: http://julieturner.net.</p>

<h3>Embedded content from other websites</h3><p>Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.</p><p>These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.</p>

<h3 id="google-analytics">Google Analytics</h3>
<p><strong>Data Used:</strong> Please refer to the appropriate <a href="https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsTrackingOverview#howAnalyticsGetsData">Google Analytics documentation</a> for the specific type of data it collects. <strong>Activity Tracked:</strong> This feature sends page view events (and potentially <a href="https://jetpackme.wordpress.com/support/for-your-privacy-policy/#video-hosting">video play events</a>) over to Google Analytics for consumption.</p>
<hr>

<h3 id="jetpack-comments">Jetpack Comments</h3>
<p><strong>Data Used:</strong> Commenter’s name, email address, and site URL (if provided via the comment form), timestamp, and IP address. Additionally, a jetpack.wordpress.com IFrame receives the following data: WordPress.com blog ID attached to the site, ID of the post on which the comment is being submitted, commenter’s local user ID (if available), commenter’s local username (if available), commenter’s site URL (if available), MD5 hash of the commenter’s email address (if available), and the comment content. If <a href="https://akismet.com/">Akismet</a> (also owned by <a href="https://automattic.com/">Automattic</a>) is enabled on the site, the following information is sent to the service for the sole purpose of spam checking: commenter’s name, email address, site URL, IP address, and user agent.</p>
<p><strong>Activity Tracked:</strong> The comment author’s name, email address, and site URL (if provided during the comment submission) are stored in cookies. <a href="https://jetpack.com/support/cookies/#comments">Learn more about these cookies</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Data Synced (<a href="https://jetpack.com/support/what-data-does-jetpack-sync/">?</a>):</strong> All data and metadata (see above) associated with comments. This includes the status of the comment and whether or not it was classified as spam by <a href="https://akismet.com/">Akismet</a>.</p>
<hr>

<h3 id="likes">Likes</h3>
<p><strong><em><span style="color:#00be28;">This feature is only accessible to users logged in to WordPress.com.</span></em></strong></p>
<p><strong>Data Used:</strong> In order to process a post like action, the following information is used: IP address, WordPress.com user ID, WordPress.com username, WordPress.com-connected site ID (on which the post was liked), post ID (of the post that was liked), user agent, timestamp of event, browser language, country code.</p>
<p><strong>Activity Tracked:</strong> Post likes.</p>
<hr>

<h3 id="notifications">Notifications</h3>
<p><strong><em><span style="color:#00be28;">This feature is only accessible to registered users of the site who are logged in to WordPress.com.</span></em></strong></p>
<p><strong>Data Used:</strong> IP address, WordPress.com user ID, WordPress.com username, WordPress.com-connected site ID and URL, Jetpack version, user agent, visiting URL, referring URL, timestamp of event, browser language, country code. Some visitor-related information or activity may be sent to the site owner via this feature. This may include: email address, WordPress.com username, site URL, email address, comment content, follow actions, etc.</p>
<p><strong>Activity Tracked:</strong> Sending notifications (i.e. when we send a notification to a particular user), opening notifications (i.e. when a user opens a notification that they receive), performing an action from within the notification panel (e.g. liking a comment or marking a comment as spam), and clicking on any link from within the notification panel/interface.</p>
<hr>

<h3 id="sharing">Sharing</h3>
<p><strong>Data Used:</strong> When sharing content via email, the following information is used: sharing party’s name and email address (if the user is logged in, this information will be pulled directly from their account), IP address (for spam checking), user agent (for spam checking), and email body/content. This content will be sent to <a href="https://akismet.com/">Akismet</a> (also owned by <a href="https://automattic.com/">Automattic</a>) so that a spam check can be performed. Additionally, if <a href="http://www.google.com/recaptcha">reCAPTCHA</a> (by Google) is enabled by the site owner, the sharing party’s IP address will be shared with that service. You can find Google’s privacy policy <a href="https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/">here</a>.</p>
<hr>

<h3 id="subscriptions">Subscriptions</h3>
<p><strong>Data Used:</strong> To initiate and process subscriptions, the following information is used: subscriber’s email address and the ID of the post or comment (depending on the specific subscription being processed). In the event of a new subscription being initiated, we also collect some basic server data, including all of the subscribing user’s HTTP request headers, the IP address from which the subscribing user is viewing the page, and the URI which was given in order to access the page (<code>REQUEST_URI</code> and <code>DOCUMENT_URI</code>). This server data used for the exclusive purpose of monitoring and preventing abuse and spam.</p>
<p><strong>Activity Tracked:</strong> <a href="https://jetpack.com/support/cookies/#subscriptions">Functionality cookies</a> are set for a duration of <strong>347 days</strong> to remember a visitor’s blog and post subscription choices if, in fact, they have an active subscription.</p>
<hr>

<h2>Your contact information</h2><p>You may contact Julie through one of the Verified Services outlined on the About Me section.</p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>692</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2018-05-18 11:53:09]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2018-05-18 16:53:09]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:post_modified><![CDATA[2018-07-22 10:42:11]]></wp:post_modified>
		<wp:post_modified_gmt><![CDATA[2018-07-22 15:42:11]]></wp:post_modified_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[closed]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[closed]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[privacy-policy]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[page]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
														<wp:postmeta>
		<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
		<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
							<wp:postmeta>
		<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_suggested_privacy_policy_content]]></wp:meta_key>
		<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:3:{s:11:"plugin_name";s:9:"WordPress";s:11:"policy_text";s:11805:"<div class="wp-suggested-text"><h2>Who we are</h2><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this section you should note your site URL, as well as the name of the company, organization, or individual behind it, and some accurate contact information.</p><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">The amount of information you may be required to show will vary depending on your local or national business regulations. You may, for example, be required to display a physical address, a registered address, or your company registration number.</p><p><strong class="privacy-policy-tutorial">Suggested text: </strong>Our website address is: https://julieturner.net.</p><h2>What personal data we collect and why we collect it</h2><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this section you should note what personal data you collect from users and site visitors. This may include personal data, such as name, email address, personal account preferences; transactional data, such as purchase information; and technical data, such as information about cookies.</p><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">You should also note any collection and retention of sensitive personal data, such as data concerning health.</p><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In addition to listing what personal data you collect, you need to note why you collect it. These explanations must note either the legal basis for your data collection and retention or the active consent the user has given.</p><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">Personal data is not just created by a user&#8217;s interactions with your site. Personal data is also generated from technical processes such as contact forms, comments, cookies, analytics, and third party embeds.</p><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">By default WordPress does not collect any personal data about visitors, and only collects the data shown on the User Profile screen from registered users. However some of your plugins may collect personal data. You should add the relevant information below.</p><h3>Comments</h3><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this subsection you should note what information is captured through comments. We have noted the data which WordPress collects by default.</p><p><strong class="privacy-policy-tutorial">Suggested text: </strong>When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor&#8217;s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.</p><p>An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.</p><h3>Media</h3><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this subsection you should note what information may be disclosed by users who can upload media files. All uploaded files are usually publicly accessible.</p><p><strong class="privacy-policy-tutorial">Suggested text: </strong>If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.</p><h3>Contact forms</h3><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">By default, WordPress does not include a contact form. If you use a contact form plugin, use this subsection to note what personal data is captured when someone submits a contact form, and how long you keep it. For example, you may note that you keep contact form submissions for a certain period for customer service purposes, but you do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes.</p><h3>Cookies</h3><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this subsection you should list the cookies your web site uses, including those set by your plugins, social media, and analytics. We have provided the cookies which WordPress installs by default.</p><p><strong class="privacy-policy-tutorial">Suggested text: </strong>If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.</p><p>If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.</p><p>When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select &quot;Remember Me&quot;, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.</p><p>If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.</p><h3>Embedded content from other websites</h3><p><strong class="privacy-policy-tutorial">Suggested text: </strong>Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.</p><p>These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.</p><h3>Analytics</h3><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this subsection you should note what analytics package you use, how users can opt out of analytics tracking, and a link to your analytics provider&#8217;s privacy policy, if any.</p><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">By default WordPress does not collect any analytics data. However, many web hosting accounts collect some anonymous analytics data. You may also have installed a WordPress plugin that provides analytics services. In that case, add information from that plugin here.</p><h2>Who we share your data with</h2><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this section you should name and list all third party providers with whom you share site data, including partners, cloud-based services, payment processors, and third party service providers, and note what data you share with them and why. Link to their own privacy policies if possible.</p><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">By default WordPress does not share any personal data with anyone.</p><h2>How long we retain your data</h2><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this section you should explain how long you retain personal data collected or processed by the web site. While it is your responsibility to come up with the schedule of how long you keep each dataset for and why you keep it, that information does need to be listed here. For example, you may want to say that you keep contact form entries for six months, analytics records for a year, and customer purchase records for ten years.</p><p><strong class="privacy-policy-tutorial">Suggested text: </strong>If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.</p><p>For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.</p><h2>What rights you have over your data</h2><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this section you should explain what rights your users have over their data and how they can invoke those rights.</p><p><strong class="privacy-policy-tutorial">Suggested text: </strong>If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.</p><h2>Where we send your data</h2><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this section you should list all transfers of your site data outside the European Union and describe the means by which that data is safeguarded to European data protection standards. This could include your web hosting, cloud storage, or other third party services.</p><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">European data protection law requires data about European residents which is transferred outside the European Union to be safeguarded to the same standards as if the data was in Europe. So in addition to listing where data goes, you should describe how you ensure that these standards are met either by yourself or by your third party providers, whether that is through an agreement such as Privacy Shield, model clauses in your contracts, or binding corporate rules.</p><p><strong class="privacy-policy-tutorial">Suggested text: </strong>Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.</p><h2>Your contact information</h2><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this section you should provide a contact method for privacy-specific concerns. If you are required to have a Data Protection Officer, list their name and full contact details here as well.</p><h2>Additional information</h2><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">If you use your site for commercial purposes and you engage in more complex collection or processing of personal data, you should note the following information in your privacy policy in addition to the information we have already discussed.</p><h3>How we protect your data</h3><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this section you should explain what measures you have taken to protect your users&#8217; data. This could include technical measures such as encryption; security measures such as two factor authentication; and measures such as staff training in data protection. If you have carried out a Privacy Impact Assessment, you can mention it here too.</p><h3>What data breach procedures we have in place</h3><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">In this section you should explain what procedures you have in place to deal with data breaches, either potential or real, such as internal reporting systems, contact mechanisms, or bug bounties.</p><h3>What third parties we receive data from</h3><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">If your web site receives data about users from third parties, including advertisers, this information must be included within the section of your privacy policy dealing with third party data.</p><h3>What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data</h3><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">If your web site provides a service which includes automated decision making - for example, allowing customers to apply for credit, or aggregating their data into an advertising profile - you must note that this is taking place, and include information about how that information is used, what decisions are made with that aggregated data, and what rights users have over decisions made without human intervention.</p><h3>Industry regulatory disclosure requirements</h3><p class="privacy-policy-tutorial">If you are a member of a regulated industry, or if you are subject to additional privacy laws, you may be required to disclose that information here.</p></div>";s:5:"added";i:1532272811;}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
							<wp:postmeta>
		<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_suggested_privacy_policy_content]]></wp:meta_key>
		<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:3:{s:11:"plugin_name";s:7:"Akismet";s:11:"policy_text";s:400:"We collect information about visitors who comment on Sites that use our Akismet anti-spam service. The information we collect depends on how the User sets up Akismet for the Site, but typically includes the commenter's IP address, user agent, referrer, and Site URL (along with other information directly provided by the commenter such as their name, username, email address, and the comment itself).";s:5:"added";i:1527690052;}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
							</item>
					<item>
		<title><![CDATA[Where to Find Me]]></title>
		<link>https://julieturner.net/me/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jturnerwp]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://julieturner.net/?page_id=1317</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<table>
<tr>
<td style="min-width: 250px;"><h2 style="padding: 0 0 0 10px; margin: 0;">Julie Turner</h2><br/>Sympraxis Consulting<br/>Partner/CTO</td>
<td><a href="https://sympraxisconsulting.com"><img src="https://julieturner.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Sympraxis-Consulting_Logo-e1663605350572.png" alt="Sympraxis Consulting Logo"/></a></td>
</tr>
</table>
<table>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://julieturner.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/twitter.png" width="32px" style="margin: 0; padding:0 10px 0 0; border-radius: 0;" alt="Twitter Logo"/> <a href="https://twitter.com/jfj1997" target="_blank" rel="noopener">jfj1997</a></td>
<td><img src="https://julieturner.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/linkedin.png" width="32px" style="margin: 0;  padding:0 10px 0 0; border-radius: 0;" alt="LinkedIn Logo"/> <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/juliemturner/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">juliemturner</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><img src="https://julieturner.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/github.png" width="32px" style="margin: 0;  padding:0 10px 0 0; border-radius: 0;" alt="GitHub Logo"/><a href=https://github.com/juliemturner/Public-Samples#readme" target="_blank">Sample Code from Talks and Blog Posts</a></td>
<td><img src="https://julieturner.net/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/greppericon.jpg" width="32px" style="margin: 0;  padding:0 10px 0 0; border-radius: 0;" alt="Grepper Logo"/> <a href="https://www.codegrepper.com/profile/julie-turner" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Zen Developer</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><h2 style="padding: 0 0 0 10px;">Podcasts/Video Shows</h2></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><a href="https://symp.info/cdc_play" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CloudDev Clarity</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2">This show is where Andrew Connell & Julie Turner can discuss, debate, and even disagree on topics specific to developers who are primarily working in the Microsoft cloud space. That includes Microsoft Azure and Microsoft 365, but it's not limited to those areas! They'll also cover topics related to these areas, like testing tools, development tools, practices, and anything else.</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><a href="https://symp.info/browser-native/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Browser Native</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2">In the Browser Native series, co-hosts Julie Turner & Bob German explore features built into all modern browsers that you might have missed if you’ve been working within a particular framework or library. Each episode includes one or more samples where you can see the code and watch it run, so it’s easy to follow along. Please join us as we level up our skills together and learn about powerful capabilities that are browser native!</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2"><h2 style="padding: 0 0 0 10px;">Open Source Projects</h2></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2">PnPjs: <a href="https://pnp.github.io/pnpjs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Documentation</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2">PnPjs is a collection of fluent libraries for consuming SharePoint, Graph, and Office 365 REST APIs in a type-safe way. You can use it within SharePoint Framework, Nodejs, or any JavaScript project. This is an open-source initiative, and we encourage contributions and constructive feedback from the community.</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2">hTWOo: <a href="https://lab.n8d.studio/htwoo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Documentation</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="2">hTWOo UI is an open-source alternative for Microsoft's Fluent UI Web Design system. hTWOo Core is a pure HTML/CSS and JavaScript implementation that can be used in any project. In addition, hTWOo React is a component-based implementation that can be used in any ReactJS project (>= React 16).</td>
</tr>
</table>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>1317</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2022-09-19 12:06:28]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2022-09-19 17:06:28]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:post_modified><![CDATA[2022-09-29 09:28:44]]></wp:post_modified>
		<wp:post_modified_gmt><![CDATA[2022-09-29 14:28:44]]></wp:post_modified_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[closed]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[closed]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[me]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[page]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
														<wp:postmeta>
		<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_last_editor_used_jetpack]]></wp:meta_key>
		<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[classic-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
							<wp:postmeta>
		<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
		<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>
	