<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Veni, Vidi, Vici</title>
    <link>https://juliemturner.net/</link>
    <description>Julie Turner Blog on Microsoft 365 (O365), SharePoint, Microsoft Teams, development and extensibility expert with SharePoint Framework (SPFx)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>Julie Turner</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>Julie Turner</webMaster>
    <copyright>2023 Julie Turner ~ All rights reserved</copyright>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
    
    <atom:link href="https://juliemturner.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    

    
    
    
    
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>JSLink Validation – from Basic to Advanced</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/jslink-validation-from-basic-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Julie Turner</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/jslink-validation-from-basic-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Custom field validation using JSLink is an extremely powerful beast. In this post I’m going to make an effort to demystify the different levels of validation you can put into your custom template and how to put it together. Everything I’m about to cover has been covered before in different ways and in different combinations. My hope is that this will help separate out what’s needed and what’s not depending on your scenario… so to that end I’ll cover three scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSLink Custom User Field Schema</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/jslink-custom-user-field-schema/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Julie Turner</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/jslink-custom-user-field-schema/</guid>
      <description>I had the requirement of setting the default value of a person field to the current user. After looking around in the great wide internet I found a very helpful article by Glenn Reian article by Glenn Reian which got me started.
Where I ran into a problem was that my user field had customized settings that weren&amp;rsquo;t being pulled through into the custom implementation of my people picker. As it turns out the issue was with the schema that is passed to the SPClientPeoplePicker_InitStandaloneControlWrapper function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SharePoint 2013 JSLink - All Fields Rendered</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/sharepoint-2013-jslink-all-fields-rendered/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 19:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Julie Turner</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/sharepoint-2013-jslink-all-fields-rendered/</guid>
      <description>While creating a custom Client Template using JSLink, I came up against the issue of knowing when all the fields were rendered on the form. To explain where the issue arises let me first take just a moment to explain when building a custom template for this type of form, where you want to manipulate the fields, you have available to you both a Pre and Post Render function. What that does is fire the function attached to it either pre or post each custom field rendering being executed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Send Email through Visual Studio Workflow in SharePoint 2013</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/send-email-through-visual-studio-workflow-in-sharepoint-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 20:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Julie Turner</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/send-email-through-visual-studio-workflow-in-sharepoint-2013/</guid>
      <description>When building a custom SharePoint 2013 Workflow using Visual Studio I ran into a very odd problem trying to send a notification email to a group of users using the Email action (specifically Microsoft.SharePoint.DesignTime.Activities.Email).
I could send email from a SharePoint 2013 workflow created using SharePoint Designer, but could not do the same from my custom workflow created in Visual Studio without the workflow throwing an error. I’m not even going to post the error because as it turns out it’s a generic error message that could show up for any number of reasons and has little to nothing to do with the problem which was partially why it took so long to solve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Primer on InfoPath and SharePoint 2010 Time Zones</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/infopath-and-sharepoint-2010-time-zones/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 13:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Julie Turner</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/infopath-and-sharepoint-2010-time-zones/</guid>
      <description>InfoPath decrepcated functions such as Today() and Now() pick up the time zone based on the settings of the SharePoint server. By default the web is set to the time zone of the server, which is thereby the default of any new sites created as well as new user profiles created. For global organizations with users around the world, there are situations where you will want the automated date/time stamps to display the local time for the user rather than the server time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InfoPath - Show links to documents in a library from the form</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/infopath-show-links-to-documents-in-a-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 20:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Julie Turner</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/infopath-show-links-to-documents-in-a-library/</guid>
      <description>I had an interesting client issue recently where the users were copying and pasting the contents of entire e-mail messages into a text box inside an InfoPath decrepcated form. Although useful in that the information was captured with the form, the implementation was tedious at best when trying to find information potentially buried there. Long story short by putting the e-mail messages in a document library that was linked to the InfoPath form library by the ID I was able to have a parent-child relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using SQL Reporting Services Report Viewer Web Part to display Access Services report.</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/sql-reporting-services-report-viewer-web-part-access-services-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 16:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Julie Turner</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/sql-reporting-services-report-viewer-web-part-access-services-report/</guid>
      <description>As you may or may not be aware when an Access database is published to a SharePoint site the reports in the database are converted into SQL Reporting Services reports. Great, you think&amp;hellip; that should mean you can host the report elsewhere in the SharePoint hierarchy simply by using the SQL Reporting Services Report Viewer Web Part. And in fact, you can, it&amp;rsquo;s just a little tricky getting it configured. Certainly not anything you can&amp;rsquo;t overcome but hopefully by posting this information it&amp;rsquo;ll help save some time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting an Application Page Title from code</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/setting-an-application-page-title-from-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 21:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Julie Turner</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/setting-an-application-page-title-from-code/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently dealing with a requirement where I need to the set an application page&amp;rsquo;s title from the code behind. By default the form has a ContentPlaceHolder control with a ContentPlaceHolderID=&amp;ldquo;PlaceHolderPageTitle&amp;rdquo; which in the master page is the text that will fall in the header&amp;rsquo;s title tag. Unfortunately, asp:Content controls are not added to the hierarchy at runtime so I can&amp;rsquo;t access it directly.
There are good ways to modify this title on the client side with Javascript but client side code doesn&amp;rsquo;t really suit my needs as the title will come from some custom manipulation that&amp;rsquo;s better done on the server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintain file version history when moving/copying files between SharePoint sites</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/maintain-file-version-history-when-movingcopying/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Julie Turner</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/maintain-file-version-history-when-movingcopying/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on a requirement to copy files from one document library to another document library in a sub-site. I figured this wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be horribly difficult to do but turns out it&amp;rsquo;s not as simple as you might think and for some reason, although I found many questions about how to do it, I found very few answers. From the things I&amp;rsquo;ve read out there it&amp;rsquo;s apparently relatively easy if you&amp;rsquo;re moving documents within the same site&amp;hellip; apparently the Move method works and I read where someone suggesting using SPExport and SPImport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add BCS Secondary Fields to a custom list definition</title>
      <link>https://juliemturner.net/post/add-bcs-secondary-fields-in-custom-list-definition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Julie Turner</author>
      <guid>https://juliemturner.net/post/add-bcs-secondary-fields-in-custom-list-definition/</guid>
      <description>When working with BCS data and creating an external data column in a list or library it is often desirable to show some or all of the secondary fields. In the SharePoint UI, this is a simple task, completed by checking off the fields to capture for viewing, searching, filtering, and sorting later.
However, when you&amp;rsquo;re building your list or library using a custom list definition schema.xml file this is not as simple.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>